FLEX X COP 2
CHARACTERS, PLACES, ORGANIZATIONS, AND EVENTS IN THIS DRAMA ARE FICTITIOUS
ALL CHILD ACTORS AND ANIMALS FILMED IN A SAFE ENVIRONMENT
There's a ghost in the abandoned house.
I'm sure it's some kind of vengeful ghost.
It's asking us to catch the killer.
- Let's go check it out. - What?
PREVIOUSLY
You check upstairs.
Nutjob!
Yes, ma'am!
What's going on?
- Hey, what happened? - I don't know.
I got attacked out of nowhere.
- One... Two, three! - Two, three!
I seriously almost died.
There really is something here.
I have great instincts, huh?
Let's open it up. There's definitely something in there.
You were there.
I started the fire.
They might've found something while putting out the fire.
Hyeonsu disappeared.
Hyeonsu's last location was that house.
You uncovered five bodies?
Yes, they're performing the autopsy now.
We performed the autopsy on the most recent victim first.
The most recently deceased victim
Had these glasses in their pants.
These belong to Park Hyeonsu.
Three months ago, at Yuseon-dong...
...Kim Minseo was murdered.
Park Hyeonsu's fingerprints were on a knife at the scene.
That knife was the knife missing from Park Hyeonsu's house.
MURDER SUSPECT
Wait, so,
The murder suspect you were after three months ago was murdered
And his body was found at the abandoned house?
What if Park Hyeonsu wasn't the one who killed Kim Minseo?
It's the perfect crime.
The target.
A victim to frame as the suspect.
If they kill the target and the suspect,
Then make him go missing,
The case cannot be solved.
Five perfect crimes.
You need at least two people to make this possible.
They're methodical and cold.
So they're professional killers?
If they came to the house...
It means they killed someone else.
They were there to bury the body.
It's blood.
KILLER 1 JANG JAECHUN
It leaked.
KILLER 2 JO BEOMKI
What do we do?
Taegwang.
THE KILLER OF KILLERS YU TAEGWANG
But don't courier deliveries come quickly
And drop it off at the door?
They're a bit different from parcel deliveries.
They usually hand it to you.
Uh-huh.
Then the victim must have known a courier was coming.
Yes, they usually contact ahead.
But this wasn't a real courier.
So someone must've helped them.
To make her open the door.
It must be the one she lives with.
Her husband.
Who is her husband?
Nam Jaeguk. He's the CEO of a furniture company.
IDENTITY RECORD NAM JAEGUK
Detective Choi, you look into Nam Jaeguk.
And check if Kim Minseo had life insurance.
- Yes, ma'am. - Detective Park.
You look into the stalking case.
Understood.
We'll meet Nam Jaeguk tomorrow.
Okay.
We're with the police.
Is Mr. Nam Jaeguk here? :cue
Yes, what is this about?
Well, his wife was brutally murdered.
Do you happen to know anything?
Like the CEO's secret, for example?
You think I'd know that?
Please take us to see him.
EPISODE 4
Don't go probing just anyone.
This is an investigation technique.
Didn't you know? Huh?
Honestly.
KIM MINSEO'S HUSBAND NAM JAEGUK
What...
Is this about?
We're here about your wife's case.
You're not the detective in charge.
We're reinvestigating the case from scratch.
Reinvestigating?
Park Hyeonsu's the culprit.
Isn't he?
Mmm. Someone else might be the culprit.
Couldn't they?
We heard your wife was being stalked.
Was the stalker Park Hyeonsu?
Yes.
I've already told the police all this.
Don't you share information?
Please tell us again.
Did you hear anything about Park Hyeonsu?
They dated briefly in college,
Then ran into each other by chance recently.
After that, he followed her around, trying to get back together.
That's what she said.
You mean your wife, Ms. Kim Minseo, said that herself?
Yes, she did. Why are you bringing this up again now?
Park Hyeonsu
Has been found.
How did you find him?
Mmm, I can't tell you. That's classified information.
We came to update you on your wife's case.
We'll be in touch.
Her husband definitely ordered the murder.
How do you know?
"I am guilty" was written all over his face.
That was pretty much a confession.
There's something else.
- What? - When we said Park Hyeonsu had been found,
He didn't ask if we'd caught him.
How did you find him?
Right, that's true.
His first concern should've been whether we'd caught the guy.
- It's because he knows the guy's dead. -  Hmm.
Hey, take care.
Where's my damn phone?
After today, you mustn't call me, no matter what happens.
During the month before Ms. Kim Minseo died,
She filed three stalking reports.
STALKING REPORT
Did you question the suspect?
No, we weren't able to.
She didn't know who it was.
She just reported that someone had been following her near her house.
Ah, for the last report,
She deliberately caused a fender bender because someone was following her.
10 DAYS BEFORE KIM MINSEO'S DEATH
Hello, we're responding to a report.
Yes, I did cause the accident, but I think that man in the car behind me
Has been stalking me for a few days now.
That's why I did it.
What are you talking about?
Hey, lady.
Why would I follow you around?
You have. You've been following me.
Lady, are you crazy? Delusional much?
But...
Both of you, please calm down.
Why would I follow you? Don't be ridiculous.
IDENTITY RECORD LEE KYUNGSU
Kyungjin, get a location on this number.
010-0675-0040. :cue
PARK HYEONSU'S HOUSE
Did you find anything?
Just some fingerprints and a few strands of hair.
- Please run them as quickly as possible. - Got it.
Hey.
KIM MINSEO 4:00 P.M.
They met three months before the incident.
Why did they meet?
They had no contact before.
Hmm...
Found it.
This is Minseo. It's been a while.
I hope you've been well.
I heard you became a lawyer.
I want to ask your advice on something.
Could we possibly meet?
I need your help.
Kim Minseo was the one who asked to meet first.
Why?
Because of this?
Look familiar?
I don't go around probing people for no reason.
It's my detective's instinct.
Understand?
Mmm-hmm. Mmm.
Who are you?
Police.
I haven't done anything wrong.
You're parked illegally, for one.
Am I getting a ticket?
Did you follow this person?
Is that your answer?
Yes, I followed her.
What about this man?
I took pictures of them meeting.
Who hired you?
How would I know that? It's just a part-time gig I do sometimes.
Besides, I don't work with them anymore.
Why not?
That woman died after I took those photos.
It kept bothering me.
It felt weird from the start.
I was told to get proof they were having an affair,
But all they did was drink coffee and talk.
They didn't even seem close.
Where was that place you worked?
I'll start the briefing.
Nam Jaeguk married Kim Minseo in 2021.
The furniture company he runs was originally his father-in-law's.
And Kim Minseo's life insurance payout
Is one billion won.
He became a CEO thanks to his in-laws.
Then killed her for the insurance payout?
Mm-mm. Mm-mm.
He's worse than that.
He even cheated on her.
With his secretary.
This is straight out of a soap opera.
Kim Minseo knew about the affair and wanted a divorce,
Which is why she met Park Hyeonsu.
Rather than get fired and end up divorced,
Nam Jaeguk chose to kill his wife.
It's clear that Nam Jaeguk was the one who hired someone to kill Kim Minseo.
The question is, who did he hire?
There's a PI involved.
A top PI, apparently. :cue
What's this?
A top PI?
The stalker Kim Minseo reported used to work here.
All he did was tail her.
He took photos of her meeting Park Hyeonsu.
He doesn't look like a top PI.
He looks kind of dopey.
His name is Myeong Seokho.
Two fraud convictions.
Let's go catch that dopey PI!
Oh. Don't you dare.
Why not?
He can just deny it.
What if he says they were just hired to tail her?
She's right.
We don't have any evidence.
Myeong Seokho may have planned it, but someone else did the work.
If we want to catch them...
We should just hire them ourselves.
Let's hire them to kill someone.
Right.
We'll plant a bug, then wait until the hitmen call.
If we trace it, we'll get their location.
Is this how you normally investigate?
Hey, it's a trade secret.
I know it seems a little weird, but it does work.
You know our track record.
Come on, we have no evidence. What if they run?
Fine. Let's try it.
Okay.
Then, shall I pose as the client?
Mm-mm. You did it last season.
We need someone who looks like they've got some kind of a past.
Did any theater as a kid?
No.
My hands start shaking when I'm dealt a decent hand in poker.
It should be someone older.
And look like they'd want someone dead.
Someone with that cold-blooded mobster vibe.
Does no one fit that bill?
What are you all doing? Where's my update?
Oh...
He looks like he could act.
- Yes, Detective Jin. -  Mr. Choi.
- I need to borrow your car. - My car?
Right now. There's no time. Send it to the station.
What are you...
We've got hitmen to catch.
There's a suit in the car, right?
I need a suit and a watch. Right now.
Stop the car.
Another car will be here shortly.
I'm sorry, sir.
Not at all.
I'm used to this.
Who is that?
Did we arrest a mob boss?
Isn't that Chief Park?
Gosh...
What are they doing?
I have no idea, sir.
There's something wrong with our whole station.
Good grief. :cue
MYEONG SEOKHO
It's really taking a nosedive.
Who are you?
Would you like something to drink?
Cold brew.
Decaf.
Light vanilla.
Toffee nut latte.
French pistachio.
Frappe, served hot.
- Fra... - Okay.
I'll go get them right away.
What in the...
How can I help you?
I've got someone to find.
I heard
You're good at finding people.
Oh, yes, well.
We are the best in the business.
What did he do?
He stole...
My stash.
What stash?
What do you think? Foot cream?
Ah.
Then, let's see.
We'll sign a contract first. Your name is?
You want to know...
My name?
The hell's wrong with you?
Uh... No.
No contract necessary.
I'll find him no matter what.
Your advance. :cue
Whoa!
You have three days.
If you haven't found him by then...
Cozy office you've got here.
Half a can of gas will wipe this place out.
If you're unlucky,
Someone might die.
I won't let you down.
Let's go.
Yes, boss.
That stings.
Have a good night, sir.
That was scary.
Chief, you were amazing. That was convincing as hell.
You should be an actor.
I was in the drama club in high school.
The Drama Lovers Club.
I knew it. You were a real scumbag.
That's a compliment, right?
Let's go.
Will he buy it, or will he not?
- That is the question. -  Let's go.
Have a good night, boss.
-  Thank you, sir. - Right, keep at it.
Hey, any movements?
No.
GANGHA 3-DONG ABANDONED HOUSE FIRE SCENE OF PAST HOMICIDE
STILL DETERMINING THE CAUSE OF THE FIRE
Fingerprints.
:cue
Looks like a burner phone.
Hey.
We got a new job. Where are you?
The reservoir?
You still haven't taken care of that?
Someone set fire to our burial site.
What are you talking about?
There were cops there.
Those useless morons.
They got scared and couldn't kill them.
They just tied them up and bailed.
But then,
Looks like someone set it on fire.
Wait, so do we make a run for it?
Why? They found nothing.
Who's the client?
I don't know.
Some kind of drug cartel. He wants me to find someone.
What's his name?
I don't know that either.
If I don't find him in three days,
He said he'll set this place on fire.
He's a cop.
A cop?
They must've found the bodies at our burial site.
Then what do we do?
Don't be scared.
They won't find any evidence.
But what about me? What do I do?
Burn all the records and go off the grid.
Your phones.
We're flying out at dawn.
Let's go on vacation.
Where do you wanna go?
- Hey, get all the files out. - What?
Get all the files out, right now!
Yes, okay.
Freeze.
Damn it.
:cue
The reservoir?
You still haven't taken care of that?
Where's this reservoir?
This is illegal wiretapping!
This won't hold up as evidence in court anyway.
You know that! Right?
You sure we won't find any evidence over there?
I doubt it.
Right now,
I'm in a real bad mood because you played me.
While we investigate that,
The real killers will get away.
Then you'll become the main culprit.
No, but... You have no evidence!
Let's see the evidence.
- What's your name? - What?
Your name.
Lee Eunjeong.
Right, Eunjeong.
Got a boyfriend?
Yes, we're planning to get married.
That's a shame.
Congratulations.
But will he wait a decade for you?
- What? - This is a hitman's office.
Over five people have been killed already.
Even if you're just a minor accomplice, you'd get at least 10 years. Right?
- Of course. - For sure.
No, I...
I don't know anything.
I just took calls and made coffee.
I don't know if the judge will believe that.
Unless you help us catch the bad guys.
Yeongil Reservoir. It's Yeongil Reservoir.
I heard Mr. Myeong mention it once.
- You idiot. - Sit down!
They would've bolted by now.
- I'll go check it out. - Got it.
-  Let's go. -  Yes, sir.
You must be in shock. Here, drink this.
Can I go home now?
Of course not. We have to question you.
What?
SEOUL GANGHA POLICE STATION
Gwangjin-gu, Seoul. Lee Eunjeong.
You're Korean, right?
I don't know.
You don't know?
You know the victim, Kim Minseo, right?
I don't know. I really don't know her.
You ordered Lee Kyungsu to tail Ms. Kim Minseo, didn't you?
Come on, stop saying you don't know. You and that dopey PI...
I really don't know.
Oh, my God, I want to go home.
They torched the whole thing.
There's a suitcase in the trunk.
It's that car.
Please keep tracking them.
Got it. :cue
There's nothing.
I need the blue light.
Detective Joo.
We got a fingerprint.
SCANNING
Jang Jaechun.
JANG JAECHUN
"Seongju State Prison."
Seongju State Prison?
2019 SEONGJU STATE PRISON
He was in the same prison as Myeong Seokho.
Let's look into Jang Jaechun.
I'll contact the prison.
I'll look into his family.
A phone was found at the reservoir.
We got a fingerprint, too.
You have an accomplice. Who is it?
Forensics will recover everything.
You know how a trial works.
Cooperating with the investigation and showing signs of remorse
Are important considerations in court.
You're out of options now.
Wouldn't it be smarter to try and reduce your sentence?
So...
His name's Jo Beomki.
He's Jaechun's old classmate.
But all I did was make the introduction.
They asked me for work.
How was I supposed to know they'd kill someone? I had no idea.
Where are they?
I really don't know.
Did you find anything?
No.
Nothing much.
Myeong Seokho named his accomplice.
JO BEOMKI
Where are they?
He doesn't know.
Find out where Jang Jaechun and Jo Beomki are.
If making introductions was really all you did,
You shouldn't go down with them. :cue
Granny.
I told you to just go to bed.
How can I go to bed when your friends are here?
- Want me to cook something? - Nah, just go to sleep already.
Help yourself.
Yes, thank you. What's this? Kimchi?
-  Thank you, Granny. Good night. -  Night.
I wish you a long and healthy life.
INCOMING CALL
Hey.
Where are you?
Somewhere safe. Why? Where are you?
I just checked into a random motel.
Then just hole up in there.
We're getting out of here tomorrow.
Where are you going?
Why do you want to know?
Hey, take me with you.
Don't be ridiculous.
I'm freaking out here.
Why are you acting like a moron?
Just lay low for a while, then make your move. Got it?
Hey, Beomki!
You bastard. You two are the ones who killed someone.
What are you going to do about this?
We're flying out of Busan first thing tomorrow.
I'll call you once I'm there.
What is it?
It's just...
We don't know where they're headed,
And catching someone at an airport isn't easy.
They're ruthless killers, so if we're not careful,
Civilians could get hurt.
We won't be able to stop them at the entrance.
It'll have to be at security.
- Notify the airport first. - Got it.
- I'll report to the chief. -  Okay. :cue
I got their location.
I got them as far as Wonsan-eup in Daegu, but nothing after that.
Wonsan-eup, Daegu?
FAMILY RECORDS JANG JAECHUN
Wonsan-eup, Daegu.
Jang's grandma lives there.
SATELLITE MAP SEARCH
4-26 DURE-GIL, WONSAN-EUP, DAEGU
That's right. I got them as far as here.
Let's go catch them now.
Let's go!
Move out.
- It'll take 3 hours and 20 minutes. - Huh?
Hold on.
That's way too long.
These guys are smart. What if they catch on and bolt?
Then what else can we do?
Yes, Detective Jin.
Mr. Choi, where are you?
I'm in the helicopter.
I was in Ulsan until now.
No way.
I need the chopper. Bring it to the station.
What?
I need to catch some hitmen.
Please be quick.
Turn the chopper around.
I'll get a car here right away.
Beomki!
If we somehow get found out,
Then we kill those two and the two of us just disappear.
If I ever call you "Beomki,"
That's the signal.
:cue
There it is.
- Get ready. - Yes, ma'am.
Yes, ma'am.
Jaechun, is that you?
What happened here?
Detective Joo.
Ma'am.
Who are you?
Stay with her.
Got it.
Ma'am, we're police officers.
What?
Why are you here? Did Jaechun do something bad again?
Well...
Yes, please send the forensics team.
They're both dead.
I need a patrol unit and an ambulance here.
There's also an elderly lady here, and she's quite shaken up.
We'll need backup.
:cue
They haven't been dead long.
- Did they kill each other? - Why? They were planning to run.
Did they get into a drunken fight?
Killing the suspects to make it the perfect crime.
There are three kinds of cigarettes.
They haven't been dead long,
So the perp's still here.
Kyungjin, don't come outside.
Oh. It's all right, ma'am. I'm sure it's nothing.
The next one's live.
Want to see who's faster, you or a bullet? Huh?
Jin Isoo!
Please.
Hold still!
I'm basically a sniper, right?
You should've aimed a little higher.
- Seriously? - Just kidding.
Good shot.
I taught you well.
That's not what's important here.
I'm basically John Wick.
Hey, are you hurt?
It's just a scratch.
Hold still. It's to stop the bleeding.
That really hurts.
Oh...
What's that?
Pain medication.
Don't give him that. He needs to suffer a bit more.
Give it to me. I'm in a lot of pain.
You asshole, you.
How dare you throw chilis at me?
Guess you couldn't outrun a bullet, huh?
Asshole. :cue
We've become a real married couple.
That's what I think.
What a lovey-dovey couple, huh?
Nice weather.
But what a shame. It's time to say goodbye.
Oh, you even had a baby?
Is it a boy, or a girl?
It's a puppy.
It was a puppy.
Nam Jaeguk.
You are hereby under arrest for soliciting the murder of Kim Minseo.
You have the right to an attorney and the right to remain silent.
You won't be penalized for remaining silent.
- Got all that? - I was just...
- I was taking a walk with my employee. - Honey.
I was just...
Did you really not know that your boyfriend killed his wife?
You don't seem that oblivious.
If you didn't know before, now you do.
Someone died because of you.
Mmm.
Is it a crime to take a walk...
Oh...
You two haven't met before, right?
Say hello. This is... No, this person.
This is the scumbag who asked you to kill his wife.
And this is the hitman who got the job.
You should become friends. You'll be cellmates soon.
Let's go.
Yes, ma'am.
They're here!
Hurry up.
Take his picture.
Here.
- Good job. Thanks. - Thank you for your hard work.
- Hey, take them away. -  Yes, sir.
Let's go.
Heaven's on my side.
Ah, another case closed.
Please look this way!
This way? Where? Like this?
It's not over yet.
Jin Isoo caught them.
It was Jin Isoo.
Now, let's walk through the case to find out what happened.
Mr. Nam Jaeguk here
Was suspicious of his wife and asked for an investigation into her movements.
- Exactly. - And Mr. Dopey...
Mr. Myeong Seokho here gave the job to Mr. Yu Taegwang.
I only made the introduction.
Sir.
Then, Mr. Yu Taegwang,
You committed a murder nobody hired you to commit.
But how did you know that Mr. Nam Jaeguk wanted his wife dead?
Are you psychic? Can you read minds?
That's exactly it.
I never asked them to kill her.
For God's sake, why did you do something so stupid?
You pieces of shit.
- What the hell did you just... - I told you.
If I go down, we all go down together.
I recorded all the phone calls.
He's called Nam Jaeguk. :cue
He's having an affair.
He wants us to kill his wife and make it look like a robbery.
Game over, loser!
-  This is a fake voice. - Get up.
Don't be ridiculous, Mr. Dopey PI.
This is AI-generated!
Want to turn yourself in? You'll feel better afterward.
It's not a crime to fall in love, right?
I've been in love, too.
It happens. We're only human.
Write down the identities of the skeletal remains you buried.
Skeletal remains?
I'm not sure what you mean.
Jang Jaechun and Jo Beomki were the ones who carried out the murders.
But they killed each other,
So your sentence won't be too harsh.
You'll be better off if you cooperate.
KIM JIHUN, OH SEA, HAN MINJAE
Let me tell you something in return.
That abandoned house you used as a burial site,
There was a robbery and murder there 10 years ago.
The killer's DNA was found at the scene,
But there was no suspect to match it against.
Why would you have used that place as a burial site?
Is it possible that was your first murder?
DNA ANALYSIS REPORT
The DNA found at the abandoned house matched your DNA.
Jo Beomki and Jang Jaechun.
You killed them too, didn't you?
And you washed the blood off in the bathroom.
We found your fingerprint there.
You thought you could play us, didn't you?
The perfect crime?
That doesn't exist.
We're sorry for everything.
The real culprit
Has been arrested.
"The brave citizen award."
"Park Ahin, of Myeongun Middle School, Grade 9, Class 1."
"In recognition of your unwavering support of
And cooperation with law enforcement, :cue
And for your assistance in the arrest of a dangerous criminal,
We award this commendation."
"February 10, 2025."
"Gwon Taegyun, Chief of Police, Gangha Police Station."
You're all here.
- Congratulations, Ahin. - Thank you.
This is a gift from me.
It's the only one in the world. Custom-made in 24-karat gold.
I'll study really hard and become a detective like you.
That might be a challenge.
The goal of a cool detective like me might be hard to reach.
Aim for Detective Joo here.
Here, let's meet again as colleagues.
Okay.
All right, back to work. I'm off.
- Sir. -  What?
- We've earned a vacation. - What do you mean?
You were just doing your duty as detectives.
Get your photos taken.
We were doing our duty, but we still busted a murder ring.
FLEX X COP 2 EPISODE 4
CONCIERGE MANAGER OH MINYEONG
Special Cast. Lee Hakju, Park Jungpyo, Kwon Seungwoo
Special Cast. Park Soi
Room 709 was unoccupied yesterday.
That room has been vacant for two months.
Why did she go to an unoccupied room alone?
- Have you seen anyone suspicious lately? - The ugly guy?
- Chunsik? - Isoo!
I asked her out.
The seventh floor camera isn't broken.
I was following the CEO's orders.
There was an assault here last Wednesday. He tried to drag her into Room 709?
It did seem like she was seeing someone lately.
I think it was one of the hotel staff.
Are you going to keep interfering?
What was he doing with the cameras off?
I found something that looks like a bloodstain.
Let's go. The suspect is on the seventh floor.
Watch out! Step on it.
Yes.
I just arrived.
I'll see you tomorrow.
The chairman is waiting for you.
I'll be leaving soon. I have no business with him.
He ordered you to come home.
Korea...
Has too many security cameras.
Translated by Hyesoo Lee